Film Stills and the History of Photography Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Photography (Box 5)
  - Luxembourg (Box 8)
    - Lippman, Gabriel, 1845-1921 (Box 8)
  - Mexico (Box 8)
    - Alvarez Bravo, Manuel, 1902- (Box 8)
    - Casasola, Augustin Victor, 1874-1918 (Box 8)
    - Casasola Archive Photos, 1900-1938 (Box 8)
    - Modotti, Tina, 1896-1942 [Slide boxes 46-47] (Box 8)
    - Orozco, Gabriel, 1962- [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
  - Nigeria (Box 8)
    - Ude, Ike, 1965- (Box 8)
  - Poland (Box 8)
    - Krull, Germaine, 1897-1985 (Box 8)
  - Romania (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Russia (Box 8)
    - Anonymous, Russian (Box 8)
    - Alpert, Max, 1899-1980 (Box 8)
    - Ignatovich, Boris, 1899-1977 (Box 8)
    - Klucis, Gustave, 1895-1944 (Box 8)
    - Langman, Elizar (Box 8)
    - Lissitzky, El, 1890-1941 (Box 8)
      XxArchitecture 19th - 20th century Russia; Painting Russia
    - Markov-Grinberg, Mark, 1907- (Box 8)
    - Rodchenko, Alexandre, 1891-1956 [Slide boxes 47-48] (Box 8)
    - Shaiknet, Arkadil, 1898-1959 [Slide box 48] (Box 8)
    - Shishkin, Arkady, 1899-1985 (Box 8)
    - Ustinov, Alexander, 1909- (Box 8)
    - Zelma, Georgi, 1906-1984 (Box 8)
  - Spain (Box 8)
    - Dali, Salvador, 1904-1988 (Box 8)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (Box 8)
  - Switzerland (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
    - Finsler, Hans, 1891-1972 (Box 8)
  - Turkey (Box 8)
    - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - United States (Box 8)
    - 19th Century (Box 8)
      Xx Photo of Eastman—photography 19th c. U.S. – Church, Fred
      - Anonymous & Various Artists [Slide boxes 48-49] (Box 8–9)
    - 20th Century [Slide box 49] (Box 9)
      - Anonymous (Box 9)
      - Ludlow Massacre (Box 9)
      - Life Magazine [Slide boxes 49-50] (Box 9)
      - Madonna: Sex [Slide box 50] (Box 9)
      - Vogue (Box 9)
        Xx for additional Fashion photos, under Commercial Design
      - Aballea, Martine, 1950- (Box 9)
      - Abbott, Berenice, 1898- (Box 9)
      - Adler, Amy, 1966- (Box 9)
      - Adams, Ansel, 1902-1984 [Slide boxes 50-51] (Box 9)
      - Adams, Dan [Slide box 51] (Box 9)
      - Adams, Mac, 1943- (Box 9)
      - Adams, Robert, 1937- (Box 9)
      - Aguilar, Laura, 1959- (Box 9)
      - Aguilera-Hellweg, Max 1955- (Box 9)
      - Albee, Wayne, act.c.1924- (Box 9)
      - Alland, Alexander (Box 9)
      - Allen, Brian, 1853- (Box 9)
      - Allen, James L., 1907-1977 (Box 9)
      - Allen, Winifred Hall, ac.1930's (Box 9)
      - Anthony, Edward, 1818-1888 (Box 9)
      - Anthony, Gene, act.c.1957- (Box 9)
      - Arbus, Diane, 1923-1971 [Slide boxes 51-52] (Box 9)
      - Arnold, Bill, 1942- [Slide box 52] (Box 9)
      - Arnold, Eve, 1913- (Box 9)
      - Austen, Alice, 1866-1952 (Box 9)
      - Avedon, Richard, 1923- (Box 9)
      - Aziz/Cucher (Box 9)
      - Babbitt, Platt, act.1854-1870 (Box 9)
      - Baker & Johnson, 1880 (Box 9)
      - Bacon, F. (Box 9)
        Xx for woodengraving of Rochester flood—under Prints U.S.—Bacon, F.
      - Baker, Isaac W. (Box 9)
      - Ball, James P. Sr., act.1825-1901 (Box 9)
        X Ball, James Presley I
        X Ball, J.P. & Son
      - Baltz, Lewis, 1945- (Box 9)
      - Balzer, Richard, act.c.1966- (Box 9)
      - Barker, George [Slide box 53] (Box 9)
      - Barnard, George, 1819-1902 (Box 9)
      - Barney, Tina, 1945- (Box 9)
      - Barrie, Ray (Box 9)
      - Battey, Cornelius W., 1875-1927 (Box 9)
      - Bayer, Irene, 1898- (Box 9)
      - Becotte, Michael, 1945- (Box 9)
      - Beals, Jessie T., 1870-1945 (Box 9)
      - Bedou, Arthur P., 1886-1966 (Box 9)
      - Bell, William (Box 9)
      - Bemis, Samuel (Box 9)
      - Beinecke, R. (Box 9)
      - Berman, Ida, 1911- (Box 9)
      - Bernal, Louis Carlos, 1941- (Box 9)
      - Bey, Dawoud, 1953- (Box 9)
      - Bing, Ilse, 1899- (Box 9)
      - Blackwell, Fred (Box 9)
      - Boughton, Alice, 1865-1943 (Box 9)
      - Blondeau, Barbara, 1938-1974 (Box 9)
      - Bourke-White, Margaret, 1904-1971 [Slide boxes 53-54] (Box 9)
      - Bradford, William, 1823-1892 [Slide box 54] (Box 9)
      - Brady, Mathew B., 1823-1896 (Box 9)
      - Brigman, Anne W., 1869-1950 (Box 9)
      - Brodsky, Michael, ca.1958- (Box 9)
      - Brooks, Ellen, 1946- (Box 9)
      - Brooks, Reva, 1913- (Box 9)
      - Brown, Dean, 1936-1973 (Box 9)
      - Brown, Laurie (Box 9)
      - Bruguiere, Francis, 1879-1945 (Box 9)
      - Buitron, Robert C., 1953- (Box 9)
      - Bullock, Wynn, 1902- (Box 9)
      - Burson, Nancy, 1948- (Box 9)
      - Cadmus, Paul, 1904-1982 (Box 9)
      - Callahan, Henry, 1912-1999 (Box 9)
      - Campus, Peter, 1937- (Box 9)
      - Capa, Robert, 1913-1954 (Box 9)
      - Carlson, Lance, 1950- [Slide box 55] (Box 10)
      - Charlesworth, Bruce, 1950 (Box 10)
      - Charlesworth, Sarah (Box 10)
      - Choate, John Nicholas, 1848-1902 (Box 10)
      - Chong, Albert, 1958- (Box 10)
      - Church, Fred (Box 10)
      - Clark, Larry, 1943- (Box 10)
      - Clegg & Guttmann (Box 10)
      - Clift, William, 1944- (Box 10)
      - Coburn, Alvin Langdon, 1882-1966 (Box 10)
      - Cole, Allen Edward, 1893-1972 (Box 10)
      - Collins, Herbert, act.1890-1920 (Box 10)
      - Coplans, John Rivers, 1920- (Box 10)
      - Corpron, Carlotta, 1901- (Box 10)
      - Corinne, Tee A., 1943- (Box 10)
      - Cowin, Eileen, 1947- (Box 10)
      - Cox, Renee, act.c.1996- (Box 10)
      - Crewdson, Gregory, 1962- [Slide box 56] (Box 10)
      - Cryer, Cary Beth, 1947- (Box 10)
      - Cumming, Robert, 1943- (Box 10)
      - Cunningham, Imogen, 1883-1976 (Box 10)
      - Curtis, Edward Sheriff, 1868-1952 (Box 10)
      - Curtis, G.E. (Box 10)
      - Cypis, Dorit (Box 10)
      - D'Alessandro, Robert (Box 10)
      - Dater, Judy, 1941- (Box 10)
      - Davidson, Bruce, 1933- (Box 10)
      - Davidson, Isaac Grundy, 1845-1922 (Box 10)
      - Davis, Billie-Louise, d.1995 (Box 10)
      - Davis, Douglas (Box 10)
      - Davis, Griffith J (Box 10)
      - Day, Frederick Holland, 1864-1933 (Box 10)
      - DeCarava, Roy, 1919- [Slide boxes 56-57] (Box 10)
      - Delano, Jack, 1914- [Slide box 57] (Box 10)
      - DeMeyer, Adolf, 1868-1949 (Box 10)
        X DeMeyer, Baron Adolf
        X DeMeyer, Adolf (Gayne), baron
      - Desoto, Lewis (Box 10)
      - Dexter, King (Box 10)
      - Di Corcia, Philip-Lorca, 1953- (Box 10)
      - Divola, John, 1969- (Box 10)
      - Dorfman, Elsa, 1937- (Box 10)
      - Dorr, Nell, 1895- (Box 10)
      - Dwyer, Nancy (Box 10)
      - Eakins, Thomas, 1844-1916 (Box 10)
        - Comparisons & Photos of Eakins (Box 10)
        - Photos by Eakins [Slide boxes 57-58] (Box 10)
      - Edgerton, Harold, 1903- [Slide box 58] (Box 10)
      - Eggleston, William, 1939- (Box 10)
      - Eisenstaedt, Alfred, 1898 (Box 10)
      - Emmet, Lydia Field, 1866-1952 (Box 10)
      - Emmons, Chansonettea, 1858-1935 (Box 10)
      - Erwitt, Elliot, 1928- (Box 10)
      - Eugene, Frank (Box 10)
      - Evans, Walker, 1903- [Slide boxes 58-59] (Box 10)
      - Expoxy Art Group, 1982- (Box 10)
      - Feininger, Andreas, 1906- (Box 10)
      - Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956 (Box 10)
      - Feininger, T. Lux, 1910- (Box 10)
      - Fellman, Sandi (Box 10)
      - Ferril, Mikki, 1937- (Box 10)
      - Fitz, Henry Jr. (Box 10)
      - Fink, Larry, 1941- (Box 10)
      - Fischl, Eric, 1948- (Box 10)
      - Fiske, George, 1835-1916 (Box 10)
      - Fitch, Bob (Box 10)
      - Fitzgibbon, J.H, ca.1816-1882 (Box 10)
      - Fontayne, C. (Box 10)
        X Fontayne, C. & Porter, W.S.
      - Frampton, Hollis, 1936-1984 (Box 10)
      - Frank, Robert, 1924- (Box 10)
      - French, Jared, 1905-1988 [Slide box 60] (Box 10)
      - Friedlander, Lee, 1934- (Box 10)
      - Friedman, Tom, 1965- (Box 10)
      - Freund, Gisele, 1912- (Box 10)
      - Gamboa, Harry Jr., 1951- (Box 10)
      - Gandert, Miguel, 1956- (Box 10)
      - Gardner, Alexander, 1821-1882 (Box 10)
        Xx for additional Civil War photographs, under O'Sullivan, T.H.
      - Garnett, William, 1916- (Box 10)
      - Gatewood, Charles, 1942- (Box 10)
      - Genthe, Arnold, 1869-1942 (Box 10)
      - Gibson, Ralph, 1939 (Box 10)
      - Gifford, Benjamin, 1859-1936 (Box 10)
      - Gilpin, Laura, 1981- (Box 10)
      - Glinn, Burt, 1925- (Box 10)
      - Gohlke, Frank, 1942- (Box 10)
      - Goldberg, Jim (Box 10)
      - Goldin, Nan, 1953- [Slide box 61] (Box 11)
      - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix, 1957- (Box 11)
      - Gowin, Emmet, 1941- (Box 11)
      - Greenfield, Lois, 1949- (Box 11)
      - Griffiths, Philip Jones (Box 11)
      - Groover, Jan, 1943- (Box 11)
      - Grove, Kathy, 1948- (Box 11)
      - Gutmann, John, 1905- (Box 11)
      - Gwen, Thomas (Box 11)
      - Haas, Ernst, 1921- (Box 11)
      - Halsman, Phillipe, 1906 (Box 11)
      - Hammond, Arthur J. (Box 11)
      - Harleston, Elise, 1891-1970 (Box 11)
      - Harris, Lyle Ashton, 1965- (Box 11)
      - Harris, Pete (Box 11)
      - Hart, Alfred A., 1816-1906 (Box 11)
      - Haun, Declan, 1937-1994 (Box 11)
      - Haynes, Gary (Box 11)
      - Heikes, Darryl (UPI) (Box 11)
      - Heinecken, Robert, 1951- (Box 11)
      - Henri, Florence, 1893-1982 [Slide boxes 61-62] (Box 11)
      - Herron, Matt, 1931- [Slide box 62] (Box 11)
      - Hesler, Alexander, 1823-1895 (Box 11)
      - Heyman, Abigail, 1942- (Box 11)
      - Hillers, John K, 1843-1925 (Box 11)
      - Hillier, James, 1915- (Box 11)
      - Hine, Lewis Wickes, 1874-1940 (Box 11)
      - Hinton, Milton, 1910- (Box 11)
      - Horst, Horst P., 1906- (Box 11)
      - Howlett, Robert, 1831-1858 (Box 11)
      - Hoyningen-Huene George, 1900-1968 [Slide box 63] (Box 11)
      - Hujar, Peter, 1934-1987 (Box 11)
      - Hyde, Scott, 1936- (Box 11)
      - Hyman, Leonard, act.1920-1930 (Box 11)
      - Iooss, Walter, 1943- (Box 11)
      - Ives, Frederick, 1856-1937 (Box 11)
      - Jackson, William Henry, 1843-1942 (Box 11)
      - Jacobi, Lotte, 1896- (Box 11)
      - Jahoda, Susan Eve (Box 11)
      - Johnston, Frances B, 1864-1952 [Slide box 64] (Box 11)
      - Josephson, Kenneth, 1932- (Box 11)
      - Kasebier, Gertrude, 1852-1934 (Box 11)
      - Kass, Deborah, 1952- (Box 11)
      - Katz, Leandro, 1938- (Box 11)
      - Kehaya, Dorothea, 1925- (Box 11)
      - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1906- (Box 11)
      - Kertesz, André, 1894-1985 (Box 11)
        - 1925 (Box 11)
        - 1926 (Box 11)
        - 1927 (Box 11)
        - 1928 (Box 11)
        - 1929 [Slide box 65] (Box 11)
        - 1930-1931 (Box 11)
        - 1932-1985 (Box 11)
      - Kesey, Ken, 1935-2001 (Box 11)
      - Kimball, Myron H., act.c.1853- (Box 11)
      - Klein, Irwin B, 1933-1974 (Box 11)
      - Klein, William, 1928- (Box 11)
      - Klett, Mark, 1952- (Box 11)
      - Kolbowski, Sylvia, 1953- (Box 11)
      - Kruger, Barbara, 1945- (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
        - Lenticular (Box 11)
          - Help (Box 11)
          - I've seen this movie before (Box 11)
          - My Hero (Box 11)
          - My Tongue is your Cheek (Box 11)
          - This is for Someone Special (Box 11)
        - Silkscreen [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
        - Photoengraving (Box 11)
      - Lange, Dorothea, 1895-1965 (Box 11)
      - Langenheim, William, 1807- (Box 11)
        X Langenheim, Wilhelm
      - Lau, Pok-Chi, 1950- (Box 11)
      - Laughlin, Clarence J., 1905- (Box 11)
      - Lavenson, Alma, 1897-1989 (Box 11)
      - Lawler, Louise, 1947- (Box 11)
      - Lee, Nikki S., 1970- (Box 11)
      - Lee, Russell, 1903-1986 (Box 11)
      - Lemieux, Annette (Box 11)
      - Leonard, Zoe, 1961- (Box 11)
      - Lesy, Michael, 1945- (Box 11)
      - Levine, Sherrie, 1947- (Box 11)
      - Levinthal, David (Box 11)
      - Levitt, Helen, 1913- (Box 11)
      - Lewenz, Lisa [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
      - Liebling, Jerome (Box 12)
      - Ligon, Glenn, 1960- (Box 12)
      - Lincoln, Fay S., 1894-1975 (Box 12)
      - Lion, Jules, 1810-1866 (Box 12)
      - Lomax, Yve (Box 12)
      - London, Jack, 1876-1916 (Box 12)
        X John Griffith
      - Lonidier, Fred (Box 12)
      - Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1956 (Box 12)
      - Lyon, Danny, 1942- (Box 12)
      - Lyons, Nathan, 1930- (Box 12)
      - Macbeth, Arthur L., 1864-? (Box 12)
      - McCarthy, Paul, 1945- [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
      - McDarrah, Fred W., 1926- (Box 12)
      - McNeill, Robert H., 1917- (Box 12)
      - Majore, Frank (Box 12)
      - Man Ray, 1890- (Box 12)
        - Groups (Box 12)
        - Heads (Box 12)
        - Nudes (Box 12)
        - Objects (Box 12)
        - Places (Streets, rooms) (Box 12)
        - Portraits [Slide boxes 68-39] (Box 12)
        - Marcel Duchamp &/ or Rose Selavy [Slide box 69] (Box 12)
        - Meret Oppenheim Photographs (Box 12)
        - Rayograms (Box 12)
      - Mann, Sally, 1951- (Box 12)
      - Manos, Constantine (Box 12)
      - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1942-1989 [Slide boxes 69-70] (Box 12)
      - Mark, Mary Ellen, 1941- [Slide box 70] (Box 12)
      - Matteson, Sumner W., 1867-1920 (Box 12)
      - Matter, Herbert, 1907- (Box 12)
      - Maude, Frederick Hamer, 1858-1960 (Box 12)
      - Mayall, John Jabez Edwin, 1810-1901 (Box 12)
      - Maynard, Carroll T., 1899-1982 (Box 12)
      - Meatyard, Ralph Eugene, 1925-1972 (Box 12)
      - Meiselas, Susan, 1948- (Box 12)
      - Mercer, R.E., ac.1900-1930's (Box 12)
      - Meredith, Ann (Box 12)
      - Martin, Roger, 1942- (Box 12)
      - Merton, Thomas, 1915-1968 (Box 12)
      - Metzker, Ray K., 1931- (Box 12)
      - Meyerowitz, Joel, 1938- (Box 12)
      - Michals, Duane, 1932- (Box 12)
      - Millan, Nestor, 1960- (Box 12)
      - Miller, Lee, 1907-1977 (Box 12)
        Xx for Portraits of, under Man Ray –Hoyningen-Huene
      - Miller, Milton M., act.1860- [Slide box 71] (Box 12)
      - Miner, Leigh Richmond, 1864-1935 (Box 12)
      - Min, Yong Soon, 1953- (Box 12)
      - Mishler, Clark, 1948- (Box 12)
      - Misrach, Richard, 1949- (Box 12)
      - Model, Lisette, 1906-1983 (Box 12)
      - Moffett, Donald, 1955- (Box 12)
      - Moon, Carl, 1878-1948 (Box 12)
      - Moore, Charles, 1931- (Box 12)
      - Morgan, Barbara, 1900-1992 (Box 12)
      - Morris, Wright, 1910-1999 (Box 12)
      - Morrisroe, Mark, 1959-1989 (Box 12)
      - Mydans, Carl, 1907- (Box 12)
      - Nagatani, Patrick & Andree Tracey (Box 12)
      - Namuth, Hans, 1915- (Box 12)
      - Nanonabah, Paul, 1944- (Box 12)
      - Natchweg, James (Box 12)
      - Nauman, Bruce, 1941- (Box 12)
      - Neidich, Warren, 1954- (Box 12)
      - Neipris, Ellen B., 1961- (Box 12)
      - Nettles, Bea, 1946- (Box 12)
      - Newman, Arnold, 1918- (Box 12)
      - Newton, Henry J., 1823-1895 (Box 12)
      - Nicosia, Nic (Box 12)
      - Nixon, Nicholas, 1947- (Box 12)
      - Norfleet, Barbara [Slide box 72] (Box 12)
      - Noskowiak, Sonya, 1900-1975 (Box 12)
      - Opie, Catherine, 1961- (Box 12)
      - O'Reilly, John (Box 12)
      - O'Sullivan, Timothy H., 1840-1882 (Box 12)
      - Outerbridge, Paul, 1896-1958 (Box 12)
      - Ownes, Bill, 1938- (Box 12)
        X William Elmo
      - Paccione, Onofrio (Box 12)
      - Palfi, Marion, 1912- (Box 12)
      - Parks, Gordon, 1912-1979 (Box 12)
      - Penn, Irving, 1917- (Box 12)
      - Pierre & Gilles (Box 12)
      - Polk, Prentice Hall, 1898- (Box 12)
      - Pollock, Henry (Box 12)
      - Poole, Paul, ac.c.1900-1940 (Box 12)
      - Porter, Eliot, 1901- (Box 12)
      - Poter, William Southgate, 1822-1889 (Box 12)
      - Post Wolcott, Marion, 1910- (Box 12)
      - Prevost, Victor [Slide box 73] (Box 13)
      - Prince, Richard, 1949- (Box 13)
      - Ragland-Njau, Phillda, 1939- (Box 13)
      - Ramos, Joe B., 1949- (Box 13)
      - Rand, Henry, 1862-1945 (Box 13)
      - Ray, Charles, 1953- (Box 13)
      - Reading, Chairman, 1930- (Box 13)
      - Richards, Eugene (Box 13)
      - Riis, Jacob A., 1849-1914 (Box 13)
        Xx for Tenement Housing Plans, under U.S. Gen.Housing –Plans; Arch.U.S. N.Y. Housing
      - Ritts, Herb (Box 13)
      - Roberts, Richard Samuel, 1881-1936 [Slide box 74] (Box 13)
      - Roberts, Wilhelmina, 1883-1976 (Box 13)
      - Robeson, Eslanda, 1896- (Box 13)
      - Robinson, Herbert F., c.1865-1956 (Box 13)
      - Rosenthal, Joe (Box 13)
      - Rosett, Jane (Box 13)
      - Rothstein, Arthur, 1915- (Box 13)
      - Rosler, Martha, 1943- (Box 13)
      - Rosskam, Edwin, 1903- (Box 13)
      - Rosskam, Louise [Slide boxes 74-75] (Box 13)
      - Rubenstein, Meridel, act.c.1978- [Slide box 75] (Box 13)
      - Ruscha, Edward Joseph, 1937- (Box 13)
      - Russell, Andrew Joseph, 1830-1902 (Box 13)
      - Ruherfurd, Louis, 1816-1892 (Box 13)
      - Safford, Monique (Box 13)
      - Samaras, Lucas, 1936- (Box 13)
      - Sarony, Napoleon, 1821-1896 (Box 13)
      - Savage, Charles Roscoe, 1832-1909 (Box 13)
      - Saxton, Joseph (Box 13)
      - Schamberg, Morton, 1881-1918 (Box 13)
      - Schell, Sherril, 1877-1964 (Box 13)
      - Scholten, John A., 19th c. (Box 13)
      - Scurlock, Addison, 1888-1964 (Box 13)
      - Scurlock, George H., 1919- (Box 13)
      - Scurlock, Robert, 1916- (Box 13)
      - Seeley, George H., 1880-1955 (Box 13)
      - Sekula, Allan, 1951- (Box 13)
      - Sengstacke, Robert, 1945- (Box 13)
      - Serrano, Andres, 1953- [Slide boxes 75-76] (Box 13)
      - Seymour, David, 1911-1956 [Slide box 76] (Box 13)
      - Shahn, Ben, 1898-1969 (Box 13)
      - Sheeler, Charles, 1883-1965 (Box 13)
      - Sheldon, Charles, ac.c.1900 (Box 13)
      - Shepherd, Harry, ac.c.1887-1904 (Box 13)
      - Shere, Sam, 1905 (Box 13)
      - Sherman, Cindy, 1954- [Slide boxes 76-77] (Box 13)
      - Shore, Stephen, 1947- [Slide box 77] (Box 13)
      - Siegel, Arthur, 1913- (Box 13)
      - Simmons, Laurie, 1949- (Box 13)
      - Simpson, Coreen, 1942- (Box 13)
      - Simpson, Lorna, 1961- (Box 13)
      - Siskind, Aaron, 1903- (Box 13)
      - Skoglund, Sandy (Box 13)
        Xx also Painting and Sculpture
      - Sleet, Moneta J., 1926- (Box 13)
      - Smith, Erwin, 1896-1947 [Slide box 78] (Box 13)
      - Smith, Hamilton, 1857-1924 (Box 13)
      - Smith, Henry Holmes, 1909- (Box 13)
      - Smith, Morgan & Marvin, ac.1930s-1950s (Box 13)
      - Smith W. Eugene, 1918-1978 (Box 13)
      - Snelson, Kenneth, 1927- (Box 13)
      - Sommer, Frederick, 1905- (Box 13)
      - Southworth & Hawes (Box 13)
        X Southworth, A.S. & Howes, J.J.
        X Southworth, Albert
      - Stackpole, Peter, 1913- (Box 13)
      - The Strans Twins (Box 13)
      - Starr, Frederick, 1858-1933 (Box 13)
      - Steichen, Edward, 1879-1973 [Slide boxes 78-79] (Box 13–14)
      - Steiner, Ralph, 1899-1986 [Slide box 79] (Box 14)
      - Sternfeld, Joel, 1944- (Box 14)
      - Stieglitz, A., 1864-1946 (Box 14)
        Xx for photograph of Steiglitz, --Cartier-Bresson—France, 20th century
        - Dorothy Norman, series (Box 14)
        - Georgia O'Keefe, series (Box 14)
        - -1899 (Box 14)
        - 1900-1915 (Box 14)
        - 1916-1922 [Slide box 80] (Box 14)
        - 1923 (Box 14)
        - 1924-1931 (Box 14)
        - 1932-1946 (Box 14)
      - Stoddard, Seneca R., 1844-1917 (Box 14)
      - Strand, Paul, 1890-1976 (Box 14)
        - Various titles (Box 14)
        - Mexican Portfolio (Box 14)
      - Strauss, Julius C., 1857-1924 (Box 14)
      - Strock, George [Slide box 81] (Box 14)
      - Struss, Karl, 1886-1981 (Box 14)
      - Sugimoto, Hiroshi, 1948- (Box 14)
      - Sunami, Souchi, 1885-1971 (Box 14)
      - Taccani, Silvia (Box 14)
      - Taylor Lonzie O., 1900-1977 (Box 14)
      - Teal, Elnora, 1900-1960 (Box 14)
      - Telberg, Val, 1910- (Box 14)
      - Tenneson, Joyce (Box 14)
      - Thayer, Abbott Handerson, 1849-1921 (Box 14)
      - Thomas, Alexander S., Ac.1860's (Box 14)
      - Thompson, Kenneth (Box 14)
      - Thorne, Harriet V.S., 1843-1926 (Box 14)
      - Traube, Arthur (Box 14)
      - Turner, Judith (Box 14)
      - Turyn, Anne (Box 14)
      - Uelsmann, Jerry N., 1934- (Box 14)
      - Ulmann, Doris, 1884-1934 (Box 14)
      - Valdez, Patssi (Box 14)
      - Van Der Zee, James, 1886-1983 (Box 14)
      - Van Dyke, Willard, 1906- [Slide box 82] (Box 14)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964 [Slide boxes 82-83] (Box 14)
      - Vargas, Kathy [Slide box 83] (Box 14)
      - Vergara, Camilo Jose, 1945- (Box 14)
      - Vishniac, Roman, 1897- (Box 14)
      - Vroman, Adam C., 1856-1916 (Box 14)
      - Walker, Christian, 1954- (Box 14)
      - Wall, Jeff (Box 14)
      - Warnecke, William, 1881-1939 (Box 14)
      - Washington, Augustus (Box 14)
      - Watkins, Carleton Emmons, 1825-1916 (Box 14)
        - New Haven (Box 14)
        - Stanford [Slide boxes 83-84] (Box 14)
      - Web, Alex [Slide box 84] (Box 14)
      - Webb, Miles, ac.1900 (Box 14)
      - Web, Todd, 1905- (Box 14)
      - Weber, Bruce (Box 14)
      - Weege, 1899-1968 (Box 14)
        X Weege(Arthur H. Fellig)
      - Weems, Carrie Mae (Box 14)
        Xx Sculpture
      - Wegman, William, 1943- (Box 14)
      - Weil, Brian [Slide boxes 84-85] (Box 14–15)
      - Weiner, Dan, 1919-1958 [Slide box 85] (Box 15)
      - Wells, Alisa, 1929- (Box 15)
      - Welling, James (Box 15)
      - Wender, Barbara, act.c.1970- (Box 15)
      - Westley, F.W. (Box 15)
      - Weston, Brett, 1911- (Box 15)
      - Weston, Edward, 1886-1958 (Box 15)
      - Wetherby, I.A., 1819-1904 (Box 15)
      - Whipple, John Adams, 1823-1891 (Box 15)
      - White, Clarence Hudson, 1871-1925 (Box 15)
      - White, Minor, 1908-1976 (Box 15)
      - Whitesinger, Anna Boyd, 1946- (Box 15)
      - Whitman, Richard Ray, 1949- (Box 15)
      - Wilke, Hannah, 1940- [Slide box 85-86] (Box 15)
      - Williams, Christopher, 1956- [Slide box 86] (Box 15)
      - Williams, Pat Ward (Box 15)
      - Winogrand, Garry, 1928-1984 (Box 15)
      - Winokur, Neil (Box 15)
      - Withers, Ernest, 1922- (Box 15)
      - Witkin, Joel-Peter (Box 15)
      - Witzel Studios (Box 15)
      - Wojnarowicz, David [Slide boxes 86-87] (Box 15)
        Xx Painting U.S.
      - Wolcott, Marion Post, 1910- [Slide box 87] (Box 15)
      - Wolfe, Louise Dahl, 1895- (Box 15)
      - Wong, H.S. (Box 15)
      - Woodbridge, Louise, 1848-1925 (Box 15)
      - Woodman, Francesca, 1958-1981 (Box 15)
      - Wozney, Chet (Box 15)
      - Wright, Holly (Box 15)
      - Zealy, J.T., 1812-1893 (Box 15)